埋葬
这里是BBC 2台
On BBC 2 now,
阿姆斯特丹的现场演出 皇家阿姆斯特丹
live from Amsterdam, the Christmas Concert
管弦乐团的圣诞音乐会…
from the Royal Amsterdam Orche--
给你拿些吃的吗
Are you picking up some food?
在节假日
Boxing Day on one
有机会享受我们的节日…
and the chance to enjoy our festive--
在半小时后 将播放马德雷山脉的宝藏
Treasure of the Sierra Madre. That's in half an hour.
首先 今晚在伦敦泰晤士河
But first, on London Thames Tonight,
艾迪·布鲁斯为您插播圣诞节新闻
we join Adie Bruce for your Christmas Day news.
今天 米哈伊尔·戈尔巴乔夫辞职
Today, Mikhail Gorbachev resigned
作为苏联的最后一任总统
as the last president of the Soviet Union.
共产主义的红旗在克里姆林宫降下
The red flag of communism lowered over the Kremlin,
从此结束了党的七十年统治
bringing to an end seven decades of the party's rule.
直到最后一刻 戈尔巴乔夫先生表达了
Right to the last, Mr. Gorbachev conveyed his unhappiness
他对苏联解体的不满
at the break of the Soviet Union.
在执政六年半后
After six and a half years in power,
戈尔巴乔夫今天宣布辞职
Gorbachev announces his resignation today
毫无疑问 因此有可能
No doubt it may have been possible
避免许多错误
to avoid many mistakes.
以更好的方式做了更多事
To have done much in a better way.
但我敢肯定...
But I'm sure...
最好是
All right, okay.
...我们共同努力将结出硕果
...our common joint efforts will yield fruit
人民将生活在一个繁荣
and our people will live in a prosperous
和民主的社会中
and democratic society.
出去吧
Go on.
我祝愿你们大家一切顺利
I wish all of you all the best.
1992年将迎来
1992 will now ring in
一位新领导人和一个新的俄罗斯
with a new leader and a new Russia.
...戈尔巴乔夫先生的成就
...Mr. Gorbachev's achievements.
布什总统中断了
President Bush interrupted
他的圣诞假期并发表声明
his Christmas holiday to make a statement
赞扬戈尔巴乔夫先生的…...
praising Mr. Gorbachev for his...
...这位前苏联总统
...former Soviet President
...不可避免地改变了历史的进程
...had inextricably altered the course of history.
女王在她的圣诞广播中...
The Queen in her Christmas broadcast...
格列佛
Gulliver?
格列
Gully?
你怎么了 嗯
What's wrong with you, hmm?
怎么了
What's wrong?
...在约瑟夫·斯大林的恐怖政权下
...under the oppressive regime of Joseph Stalin
导致了与西方的所谓“冷战”
led to the so called 'Cold War' with the West.
昨天，戈尔巴乔夫向克里姆林宫的工作人员
Yesterday, Mr. Gorbachev said his fond farewells
进行了亲切的告别，但在首都的街道上
to staff at the Kremlin, but on the streets of the capital
几乎没有人为这位前国家元首悲伤
few tears were shed for the former head of state,
许多人仍在承受他经济失败的冲击
as many are still feeling the brunt of his economic failures.
嘘
Psst.
放开我
Let me go.
不 我不会那样做
No, I'm not going to do that.
特别是在你对格列佛做了什么之后
Especially after what you did to Gulliver.
我只是给他下了药
I only drugged him.
放开我
Let me go.
放开我 你他妈的婊子
Let me go, you fucking bitch!
他妈的
Fucking-- ah!
你为什么闯进我家
Why did you break into my house?
要从我这里偷东西
To steal from me?
或者你来这里是
Or are you just here to act out violence against another Jew?
对一个犹太人施暴
against another Jew?
哦 我知道你是谁
Oh, I know what you are.
这很真正常
That's quite obvious.
要怎样 你…你…
So is that it? You--
你闯进来了…要杀我 强奸我
you broke in to-- to hack me, to rape me?
- 你他妈有病  -不
-That's fucking sick. -No.
把纳粹死亡集中营的人名纹成号码 太恶心了
Tattooing Nazi bile as a death camp number, that is sick.
11- 23 是啤酒馆起义的日期
11-23, the date of the Beer Hall Uprising.
88 希特勒
88, heil Hitler.
你很可悲 也很明显
You're as obvious as you are pathetic.
怎么样 嗯 你知道那是什么吗
How about this, huh? You know what that is?
哈哈
No.
是的 我敢打赌你会的
Yeah, I bet you do.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
嗯 安娜·马歇尔
Mm, Anna Marshall.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
卡尔·爱德华兹
Karl Edwards.
哪个白痴还会把他的身份证也带着
What idiot brings his ID to a break-in?
现在
Well...
尽管这一切都很有趣 但我认为应该
As amusing as all this is, I think it's time
把你交给警方
to introduce you to the police.
是的 没错 安娜·马歇尔
Yeah, right. Anna Marshall.
你以前是谁呢
What about who you used to be?
布拉纳·瓦西里耶娃·布罗德斯卡娅
Brana Vasilyeva Brodskaya.
苏联翻译
Soviet translator.
我知道你的秘密 布拉纳
I know your secret, Brana.
没什么秘密 我是苏联人
What secret? That I was a Soviet?
冷战已经结束 你没看过新闻吗
The Cold War is over. Haven't you seen the news?
我知道你在柏林发现了什么
I know what you found in Berlin.
紧急情况话务员 您需要什么服务
Emergency service operator. Which service do you require?
我就知道 我他妈的知道
I knew it. I fucking knew it.
布雷斯劳的老人说的是实话
The old man in Breslau was telling the truth.
布雷斯劳·弗罗茨瓦夫
Breslau? Wroclaw.
没有人相信他的疯狂故事 但我相信了
No one believed his crazy story, but I did.
我做到了 我他妈的找到了你
I did and I fucking found you!
什么老人 什么故事
What old man? What story?
战争的故事
The story of the war.
最后
The very end of it.
一群苏联士兵
A group of Soviet soldiers
还有一名女情报军官和他们在一起
and a female intelligence officer with them.
他们在总理府的掩体旁发现了一些东西
They found something by the bunker at the Chancellery
一些非常重要的东西 他们接到命令
Something so important they were ordered
亲自将其送回莫斯科
to deliver it back to Moscow personally.
秘密的
Secretly.
老人发誓他不知道他们携带了什么
The old man swore he didn't know what they were carrying,
但这足以让他们被杀掉
but it was enough to get them killed.
说他们都被消灭了
Said they all got wiped out.
除了一个人 其他人都没了
All except one, that is.
你想从我这里得到什么
What do you want from me?
历史是由胜利者书写的
History is written by the victors.
你听说过吗
You ever hear that?
我想知道真实的历史
I want to know the real history.
真相
The truth.
你和你的俄罗斯朋友
That you and your Russian friends
发现了希特勒逃跑的证据
found evidence of Hitler's escape
你们试图掩盖它
and you tried to cover it up.
你们找到了他幸存下来的证据
You found evidence that he survived,
甚至知道他去了哪里
maybe even where he went
然后你把它运送给斯大林
and you ferried it back to Stalin.
你本来可以的 但你被抓了
Or you would have, but you got caught.
够了 够了
Stop it. Stop it.
他妈的够了 够了
Fucking stop it! Stop it!
这他妈的是什么
What the fuck is that?
这是事实
This is the truth.
这就是真相
In here is the truth.
但恐怕这并不完全是你所期望的
But I'm afraid it's not quite what you expect.
在我的一生中，我见过很多人:
You see, throughout my life I've seen so many men
在说出真相时
offer the truth
骄傲地指着
proudly pointing
一些看似无关紧要的事情
to some seemingly insignificant thing
然后说“这就是你所看到的一切
and saying, "This is all that you see.
这就是罪魁祸首
This is what to blame.
这会治好你所有的病
This will fix all your ills
让你获得自由
and set you free."
但他们都是江湖骗子
But they're all charlatans.
骗子们争先恐后地争夺权力
Con-men scrambling for power.
在每种情况下 人们最终
And in every case, people would eventually
都会认清这个把戏
recognize the trick.
他们会清楚地看到
And they'd see with clear eyes
这个神奇的包治百病的灵丹妙药...
that this magical cure-all...
只不过是一个…
was nothing but a--
一个空盒子
an empty box.
什么…
What the--
那他妈的是什么
what the fuck was that?
他妈的就是这个吗
The fuck is that?
你给我下了药
You drugged me.
是的 我恐怕不能简单地
Yeah. I'm afraid people like you
告诉你这样的人真相
can't simply be told the truth.
要真正理解 你必须直接体验
To truly understand it, you have to experience it.
你必须去感受它
You have to feel it.
你坐得舒服吗
You sitting comfortably?
接着我会告诉你我的故事
Then I'll tell you my story.
在那场可怕战争的最后几天
Of the last days of that horrible war.
在柏林沦陷后
After Berlin had fallen,
但在它真正结束之前
but before it truly ended.
是的 我是一名俄国军官
I was, yes, a Russian officer.
我接到命令
And I was given orders,
是秘密任务
this secret task.
但我们真正发现的并不是你想的
But what you think is not what we really found,
我们牺牲了一切
what we sacrificed everything for.
我竭尽全力
I tried so hard to do what was right.
去做正确的事
to do what was right.
柏林 1945年
布罗德斯卡娅中尉同志
Comrade Lieutenant Brodskaya.
上校同志
Comrade Colonel.
计划发生了变化
There's been a change of plan.
不再选择乘飞机运输
Transport by plane is no longer an option.
看起来我们得步行
Looks like we're walking.
伊利亚索夫上尉和他的手下
Captain Ilyasov and his men
将护送我们前往波兹南
will escort us to Poznan
与彭科夫斯基会合
to rendezvous with Penkovsky
登上前往莫斯科的火车
and board a train to Moscow.
有问题吗 布拉纳
Speak, Brana.
这相当于一天的车程
That's over a day's drive.
可能更长
Longer, probably.
大部分时间我们将步行
We'll be on foot for most.
我认为时间至关重要
I thought that time was of the essence.
更重要的是
It is far more important
尽可能悄无声息地把它拿回去
to get it back as quietly as possible,
甚至我们在柏林的同志也不知道
Not even our comrades in Berlin can know,
因此没有航班 也没有通信
hence no flights and no communications.
这东西是一个定时炸弹
This thing is a ticking bomb
如果我们不太小心
liable to blow up in our faces
就会在我们面前爆炸
if we are not too careful.
仅限我们三个人知道这项任务
Only the three of us know of this business.
让我们严守秘密
Let's keep it that way.
哦 你们是唯一知道的
Oh, and of course number one knows.
你们俩记住
Remember that, both of you.
斯大林已经亲自给了我们这个命令
Stalin himself has given us these orders.
不要让他失望
Don't let him down.
-是的上校同志 -是 上校同志
-Yes, Comrade Colonel. -Yes, Comrade Colonel.
很好
Good.
《真理报》否认这些谣言的谎言
Pravda denies these rumors as lies.
但是 尽管柏林沦陷了
But despite the fall of Berlin,
德国最高统帅部仍拒绝投降
German high command still refuses to surrender
战斗在全国各地继续进行
and fighting continues across the country.
现在 比以往任何时候都更加…
-Now, more than ever...
我很庆幸
I'm celebrating.
庆幸什么
Celebrating what?
能活着离开柏林
Making it out of Berlin alive.
纳·兹多罗维
Na Zdorovie.
我们每天晚上都要这样做吗
We have to do this every night?
不只是我们 格里戈里
Not we, Grigoriy.
你也来 艾欧西夫
You too, Iossif.
约瑟夫 过来帮他把这个东西埋了
Iossif, get over here and help him bury this thing.
给你
Here.
你不好奇里面有什么吗
You're not curious what's inside it?
帮帮我吧 好吗
Just help me with it, will you?
你不觉得这很奇怪
You don't think that's strange,
我们每天晚上都要埋葬一回
we have to bury it every night?
我想这会给我们带来麻烦
I think you're gonna get us in trouble.
我站起来 我会转过他的头
I get my foot and I'll flip his head.
又做噩梦了
New nightmares?
还是那样
Or old?
新的
New.
好运
Lucky.
自从柏林出来
Since Berlin.
似乎无法摆脱
Can't seem to get rid of them.
那就不睡觉
Don't sleep.
我能问你一个问题吗
Can I ask you a question?
为什么我们每天晚上都把它埋了
Why do we bury it every night?
我能问一下 米哈伊尔·伊万诺维奇
Can I ask you, Mikhail Ivanovich,
为什么别人叫你托尔
why do the others call you Tor?
保密吗
It's hidden.
如果有人把我们在睡梦中杀了
Someone kills us in our sleep,
他们可能仍然找不到它
they still might not find it.
就像我说的 不要睡觉
Like I said, don't sleep.
说说你的名字
And the name?
在斯大林格勒
In Stalingrad
我用锤子杀死了一些党卫军装甲兵
I killed some Panzer SS with a hammer.
托尔
Tor.
北欧雷神
Norse god of thunder.
他拿着把锤子
He had this hammer.
所以他们给你起了个北欧名字
They gave you a Norse name?
给了一个斯拉夫人
Gave you a Slav one.
这是希伯来语
It's Hebrew.
你为什么用锤子
Why did you use a hammer?
这就是我当时能找到的唯一东西
It's all I could find at the time.
你找到了吗
Did you find it yet?
继续寻找
Keep looking.
布罗德斯卡娅中尉
Lt. Brodskaya.
中尉
Lieutenant.
布拉纳 起床
Brana! Get up.
是挖出死者的时候了
Time to dig up the dead.
来吧 起来
Come on, get up.
我们走
Let's go.
我想那口井又干涸了
I guess that well has run dry again.
是的
Yeah.
欢迎回到波兰
Welcome back to Poland.
往后点
Keep off the back.
-继续推 -好
-Keep pushing! -Right.
-推 -继续推
-Push! -Keep pushing!
继续推动
Keep pushing!
-鼓足劲 -开始吧
-Push up! -Here we go.
-来吧 -来吧
-Come on! -Come on!
我们不想再次陷入困境
We don't want to get stuck again.
我们会在夜幕降临时到达波兹南郊区
We'll reach the outskirts of Poznan by nightfall.
有足够的时间赶上最后一班火车
Should be enough time to make the last train.
不 我认为这不是一个好主意
No, I don't think that's a good idea.
我们要在黑暗中行驶
We'll be driving in the dark.
我们应该在这里找个地方露营
We should find somewhere to camp around here.
我们有足够的时间去城里
We have plenty of time to get to the city.
最好是--
-Better to get to the--
下车 卧倒
-Get down! Get down!
找掩护
Take cover!
狙击手 单射手
Sniper. Single shooter.
在哪
Where?
他到底要去哪里
Where the hell is he going?
-德国人 -你确定不是波兰人
-German. -You sure? Not Polish?
狼人
Werewolf.
这很不好
That's not good.
我们应该重新上路
We should get back on the road.
不行
No.
-我们需要埋葬尸体 -为什么
-We need to bury the body. -What?
不行 可能还有更多 更多的狼人
No. There could be more out there. More werewolf.
只是一个拿着普鲁士战争步枪的老人
It's just an old man with a rifle from the Prussian War.
我们应该留下埋葬我们的同志
No, we stay, we bury our comrade.
除非你要使我们上校同志受辱
Or would you rather dishonor our Comrade Colonel
才把他留在路边
by leaving him on the side of the road?
我们在这里宿营
We make camp here.
托尔
Tor.
-你过来 负责执行埋葬 - 昨晚就是我做的
-You're up. Burial duty. -I did it last night.
那你就会越做越好了 对吧
Then you'll be getting good at it, won't you?
我们还有时间到达约定地点
We still have time to make the rendezvous.
不了 我们住在这里
No, we're staying here.
就这样结束了
And that's the end of it.
我现在负责
I'm in charge now.
你们去哪儿
Where are you going?
在这里附近的村庄里寻找补给品
To find supplies in the village near here.
-你不能去 -怎么不能
-You can't. -Can't?
我的意思是 我们不应该去
I mean, we shouldn't.
这样不安全的 这里需要我们保护
It's not safe. We need to guard this.
您可以在这保护
You can protect it.
但是我们的命令 你应该…
But our orders. You're supposed to--
好吧 有三个人留下
Fine, you take these three
他们还可以保护你 瓦西里耶娃
and they can protect you, Vasilyeva.
团体分散是不安全的 伊利亚索夫
It's not safe to split up the group, Ilyasov.
可环顾下四周 这里并没有人
Look around you. There's no one here.
没有人看到 没有人发现
There's no one watching. No one cares.
战争结束了
The war is over.
-战争还没有结束 -我们结束了
-The war is not over. -Ours is.
而你 你剥夺了我们
And you, you've ripped us
应得的庆祝 你欠我们的
from our well-earned celebrations, so we're owed.
战利品
Spoils of war.
应该欠了我们很多
We're owed that much at least.
别担心 我们会小心的
But don't worry, we'll be careful.
我们会保持安静
We'll be quiet.
我们只是去找个温暖的地方
We're just gonna go and find some warmth.
然后我们直接回来
And then we'll come straight back.
傻瓜
Damn fool.
说什么呢
What was that?
狼人呢
What about the werewolf?
别担心 瓦西里耶娃
Don't worry, Vasilyeva.
今晚没有满月
There's no full moon tonight.
别听信他
Don't believe him.
战利品
Spoils of war.
我很清楚知道这意味着什么
I know exactly what that means.
你来坐下吗
You want to sit down?
天知道他会惹出什么麻烦
God knows what kind of mess he'll cause.
那我们也过去吧
Let's go get the back then.
我们不能放任不管
We can't leave it unguarded.
好吧 那我去
Well, then I'll go.
一个人
Alone.
他能听你的吗
He'll listen to you?
让我去 你留下来照顾板条箱
I'll go. You stay and look after the crate.
他会听你的吗
He'll listen to you?
他会听的
He'll listen.
你知道 我母亲在我父亲没有回家时
You know, my mother used to have that exact same look
曾经也是这个样子
when my father didn't come home.
哦 是吗
Oh, yeah?
你父亲的最后怎样
How'd that work out for your father?
留在这里
Stay here.
开门
Open up!
对不起 小酒馆关门了
Sorry, tavern closed.
不行 不能关
No, it's not.
干杯
Na Zdorovie!
哇
Whoa!
不要撒了
Don't waste it!
哦 她才来了 你去哪里了
Oh, here she comes. Where've you been?
我以为你是去后面杀了一头猪
I thought you were out the back killing a pig.
那是什么 猪肉
-What's that? That pork?
哦 对了 想尝尝吗
Oh, right, want some of that?
有几天没吃了
Days old.
嘿
Hey.
这里就你一个人
You the only one here?
一个人就够了
I get more.
好 再去多拿点来
Yeah, go get some more.
你想去哪里
Where you going?
嗯
Hmm?
你知道 托尔
You know, Tor,
我要感谢你
I want to thank you
主动提出把我留在这
for offering to leave me here
女人与孩子中间
with the woman and the boy.
你总是想逃避家务 格里戈利
You always try to get out of your chores, Grigoriy.
是的
Yeah.
跟你们俩说话
It is a chore making conversation
也是件苦差事
with you two.
那是什么
What is that?
随便看看
Werewolf light reading.
你之前说过狼人
You talked about werewolves before.
狼人
Werewolf.
你以为他们说的真有狼人吗
You think they were talking about real werewolves?
不 我...
No, I...
嘿 嘿 别逗他
Hey. Hey. Ignore him.
这是戈培尔想出的一个可怕的名字
It's Goebbels' idea of a more frightening name.
让他们听起来比他们本身更有威胁性
Make them sound more threatening than what they are.
老人和希特勒青年拿着刀和棍子
Old men and Hitler youth with knives and sticks
躲在森林里
hiding in the forest.
是那些不肯放弃战斗的傻瓜
Fools who won't give up the fight.
殉葬者
Memento Mori.
这是拉丁语
It's Latin.
你会说拉丁语吗
You speak Latin?
不 我…
No, I--
我只知道是什么意思
I just know what it means.
这很好 艾欧西夫
That's good, Iossif.
你显然是一个受过教育的年轻人
You're obviously an educated young man.
不像我们
Not like us.
这词是什么意思
What does it mean?
记住死亡
Remember death.
在罗马 当士兵们从胜利的战场上返回家园时
In Rome, when soldiers returned home from victorious battle,
人们曾经对他们大喊大叫着
people used to shout this at them.
记住死亡
Remember death.
他们刚刚打败对手  躲过了死亡
They just defeated armies and cheated death
所以需要被提醒他们仍然是凡人
and so needed to be reminded they were still mortal men,
不是神
not gods.
记住死亡 会降临到我们所有人身上
Remember death comes to us all.
你知道 当我们经过这里时
You know, when we passed through here,
我们就离这不远了
we weren't far off this.
禁止入内
我们想要为鲜血 为德国人
We wanted blood, revenge
对我们的所作所为复仇
for what the Germans had done to us.
我们变成了他们害怕的样子
We became what they feared.
他们会怎样描绘我们
What they painted us to be.
怪物
Monsters.
然后…
Then--
然后我们发现了他们的死亡集中营
then we found their death camps.
你见识过他们的能耐
You saw what they were capable of.
现在已经没有什么胜仗了 艾欧西夫
There's no such thing as victorious battle anymore, Iossif.
在这场战争中
Not in this war.
任何一个活下来的人
Anyone who survives it,
是不需要什么死亡提醒
won't need any reminder of death.
-伊利亚索夫 -上帝
-Ilyasov. -Jesus!
这不关你的事
This doesn't concern you.
走 离开这里
Go, get out of here.
你在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
听我说 你这头猪
Listen to me, you pig!
你现在醉酒的鲁莽行为
Your reckless, drunken behavior is now
正在危及我们的使命
endangering our mission.
嘿
Hey!
你认为你能这样跟我说话吗
Who do you think you are talking to me like that?
你知道 我是哪的人
You know, where I'm from,
女人不能这样和男人说话
women don't talk to men like this.
放开我
Get off me.
你破坏我的兴致 嗯
Spoil my fun, eh?
我 你这头肮脏的猪
Get off me, you filthy pig.
也许我应该给你一个教训 嗯
Maybe I should teach you a lesson instead, eh?
他妈的 混蛋
Fucking hell!
哦 你这个婊子
Oh, you bitch!
放下你的枪
Lower your gun.
放下
Lower it.
别动
Don't.
你会说德语吗
You speak German?
你会吗
So do you.
杀死他妈的这个纳粹分子
Kill this fucking Nazi.
我一会儿再跟你算账
I'll deal with you in a second.
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
我住在附近 我听到了尖叫声
I live near here. I heard screaming.
是不是只有你
Was it just you-
那是什么
What was that?
-是小酒馆 -离开
-It came from the tavern. -Move.
离开
Move!
这个地方着火了
The place is on fire!
伊利亚索夫 等等
Ilyasov, wait.
伊利亚索夫 回来
Ilyasov, get back.
马卡尔
Makar!
这里到底发生了什么
What the hell happened here?
我们应该离开
We should leave.
迪米特里 你没事 你没事
Dimitry! You're okay, you're okay.
你能说话吗
Can you talk?
你能听到我说话吗
Can you hear me?
发生了什么事
What happened?
烟
Smoke.
毒
Poison.
这是谁干的
Who did this?
我不知道
I don't know.
狼人
Werewolf.
为什么这么说呢
Why do you say that?
他们躲在森林里
They hide in the forest.
窥测镇上
Watch the town.
他们使用这样的办法
They use tactics like this.
燃烧地衣和蘑菇
They burn lichen and mushroom.
让你产生幻觉
Makes you hallucinate.
让你看到一些东西
Makes you see things.
我把他们吓跑了
I scared them off.
有多少人 马卡尔
How many, Makar?
我不知道
I don't know.
窥测镇上什么?
Watch the town for what?
俄罗斯人
Russians.
喜欢你
Like you.
弗里茨可能是其中之一
Fritz is probably one of them.
-他是波兰人 伊利亚索夫 - 然后他的正义
-He's Polish, Ilyasov. -Then he's AK.
可能直接把他们引到我们这里来
Probably led them straight to us.
引他们来找我们的那就是你 瓦迪姆
If anyone led them to us, it's you, Vadim.
-这是你的错 -我的错
-This is your fault. -My fault?
我告诉过你不要离开板条箱
I told you not to leave the crate.
在森林出现狙击手之后 我们应该…
After the sniper in the forest, we should have--
森林
The forest.
格里高利
Grigoriy.
艾欧西夫
Iossif.
托尔
Tor?
格里沙
Grisha.
格里高利
Grigoriy.
托尔
Tor?
嘿
Hey.
向上
Up.
爸爸
Papa?
艾欧西夫.艾欧西夫.
Iossif. Iossif.
是我 是我 是我
It's me. It's me. It's me.
你没事 你没事 烟雾
You're okay. You're okay. The smoke.
是烟
It's the smoke.
它让你看到东西
It makes you see things.
看 看 没关系 其他人在哪里
Look. Look, it's fine. Where are the others?
托尔和格里高利在哪里
Where's Tor and Grigoriy?
卡车不见了
Truck's gone.
狗屎
Shit.
让我们拿起板条箱 离开这里
Let's get the crate and get out of here.
什么 步行
What, on foot?
把你的枪给我
Give me your gun.
你让她拿我的枪
You let her take my gun.
我帮你拿武器
You need me armed.
你帮我搬这个
I need you to help carry this.
什么 一直搬到波兹南
What, all the way to Poznan?
不 我们应该留下来与这些农民狗作斗争
No, we should stay and fight these peasant dogs.
这些狗溜了过来，杀了我们两个人
These dogs managed to sneak up and kill two of ours.
三个
Three.
找到了格里戈里
Found Grigoriy.
你是个懦夫 我们应该站起来战斗
You're a coward. We should stand and fight.
你又忘记了我们被派来做什么
And you're forgetting again what we were sent to do.
不交火 不制造动静
Not to fight, not to make noise.
就为了保护这个
To protect this.
这是怎麽 你在谈论什么
What's this? What are you talking about?
我们不能一直带着它
We can't carry it all the way,
我们可以找到一个地方把它藏起来
but we can find somewhere to stash it.
隐藏的地方
Somewhere to hide.
我们能回到村子里吗
Can we make it back to the village?
我们会太暴露了
We'd be too exposed.
我可能知道个地方
I might know somewhere.
安全的地方
Somewhere safe.
托尔在哪里
Where's Tor?
你进行最后一次搜索 看看是否能找到他
Make a last sweep. See if you can see him.
如果他还活着 他会来找我们
If he's still alive, he'll find us.
帮帮我这个
Help me with this.
你被告知要等待
You were told to wait.
他们分手了
They split up.
我们借此机会把他们分成更小的小组
We took the chance to take them in smaller groups.
你拿走了吗
And did you take them?
少数人可能已经逃脱了
A few may have escaped.
五月 我不确定这是如何从地下挖出来的
May? I'm not sure how this digs itself out of the ground.
比我们预期的要多
There were more than we expected.
这就是为什么我告诉你要等
Which is why I told you to wait.
-我们会找到他们的 -它
-We'll find them. -It!
找到它 杀了他们
Find it. Kill them.
等
Wait.
也许你和你的手下会有更好的运气
Maybe you and your men will have better luck
用我们带来的武器
with the weapons we brought.
它很接近
It's close.
我能感觉到
I can feel it.
嘿 停下
Hey, stop.
停
Stop.
你和他们在一起吗
Are you with them?
德意志
Deutsche?
波兰人
Polskie?
我不会伤害你 好吗
I'm not going to hurt you, okay?
你在这里做什么
What are you doing out here?
嘿 我需要找到我的人
Hey, I need to find my people.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
住手 我说我不会伤害你
Stop! I said I wouldn't hurt you.
我现在就让你走
I'm going to let you go now.
但如果你尖叫
But if you scream
我必须阻止你 你明白吗
I'll have to stop you. Do you understand?
你来自村里 是的 维斯卡
You are from the village, yes, Wioska?
是的 来自村里
Yes, from village.
所以你理解我吗
So you do understand me?
我需要你给我带路
I need you to show me the way there.
我需要找到像我们的其他人
I need to find the others like me.
如果你跑或试图向任何人发出信号…
If you run or try and signal anyone--
明白
Yes.
你明白我说吗
You understand me?
是的
Yes.
好吧
All right.
是的 没错
Yeah, right.
就是那个地方
That's the place?
是的 我们在那里会安全
Yeah, we'll be safe there.
住在那里的人 他们是好人
The people that live there, they're good people.
友善
Kind.
他们会帮助我们
They'll help us.
上一次俄罗斯人来到这里
Last time Russians came through here,
他们像这样杀了人
they murdered people like this.
说是为了帮助我们
Just for helping.
向我保证你和其他人不一样
Just promise me you're not like the rest of them.
只要你向我保证你和其他人不一样
If you promise me you're not like the others.
在那边
Out there.
好
Okay.
在这里等一下
Wait here.
我怀疑我们是否还能见到
I doubt we'll see him again.
站住
Stop that.
他在帮助我们
He's helping us.
什么 弗里茨
What, Fritz?
你相信他 是吗
You trust him, do you?
比你还相信 伊利亚索夫
More than I trust you, Ilyasov.
上尉同志
Comrade Captain.
别忘了你从哪里来 姑娘
Don't forget where you're from, girl.
我不会忘记我是来自哪里的人
I'm not the one forgetting where I'm from.
或者我接受的命令是什么
Or what my orders are.
如果我们能回到我们俩来的地方
And if we make it back to where we're both from,
如果我们活着离开这里
if we make it out of here alive,
我一定会让他们知道你做了什么
I'll make sure they know that your behavior
你直接违背了我们的命令
directly went against our orders.
你杀了那些人
That you got those men killed
并危及我们的任务 上尉同志
and jeopardized our mission, Comrade Captain.
和我保持距离 伊利亚索夫
Just keep your distance from me, Ilyasov
我不喜欢和你这么近
I don't enjoy being this close to you.
那么 你在森林里到底在做什么呢
So what are you doing all this way out in the forest?
哼
Huh.
你晚上还在树林里跑来跑去吗
Still, you're running about in the woods at night?
我要从你身边逃跑
I run from you.
从我这逃跑
From me?
为什么
Why?
为和你同样进村的布尔什维克
Bolsheviks like you who come into village.
德国人呢
What about the Germans?
涅米耶茨基
Niemiecki,
躲在森林里 你了解他们吗
hiding in the forest, do you know about them?
嘿 是躲在这片森林里的德国人吗
Hey, hey, what about the Germans hiding in this forest?
-狼人 -是的
-Werewolf? -Yes.
狼人
Werewolf.
你不怕他们吗
You're not afraid of them?
不
No.
嘿 停下
Hey, stop.
他们不像布尔什维克那么坏
They are not as bad as Bolsheviks.
你不要说这样的话
Don't you say things like that.
你很幸运 你碰到了我 而不是别人
You're lucky you bumped into me and not one of them.
你不知道你在说什么
You don't know what you are talking about.
你不知道
You have no idea.
你不知道他们是什么样的
You don't know what they're like.
我知道你是什么样的
I know what you are like.
布尔什维克 德国人 都是一样的
Bolsheviks, Germans, both the same.
现在德国人走了
Only Germans have gone now.
可布尔什维克来了
Bolsheviks have come.
杀人 强奸
Murdering, rape.
杀死我的父母
Killing my parents.
因为谎言
For lies.
为了帮助德国人
For helping Germans.
帮他们就好像别无选择
Helping like they had any choice.
我不怕德国人
I'm not afraid of Germans.
它们不再是威胁
They are not a threat anymore.
因为我们把他们赶了出去
Because we forced them out.
谁会把你赶出去
And who will force you out?
走
Go.
我会找到我的方式
I'll find my way.
走 我让你走了
Go. I'm letting you go.
村庄就是这样
Village is that way.
-下来
-Down!
趴下
Get down.
Get down!
不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no.
不 不 来吧 加油 不
No, no, come on. Come on. No.
不 不 不 请
No, no, no. Please.
哈哈不 不 不
No. No, no, no.
请
Please.
嘿
Hey.
没关系 没关系
It's okay. It's okay.
我们需要您的帮助
We need your help.
不 不 不 那里没有尸体
No, no, no. There's no body in there.
哈哈
No.
-你在做什么 -我们需要他们的帮助
-What are you doing? -We need their help.
好吧 给他们一把枪
Well, put a gun on them.
那是
Is that?
他是在柏林的地堡里
He shot himself
开枪自杀的
in his bunker in Berlin.
《真理报》说 关于他死亡的报道是谎言
Pravda said reports of his death were lies.
-他们不是 -你怎么知道
-They weren't. -How do you know?
我们确定了
We made sure.
有牙科记录
Dental records.
现在您明白了为什么我们需要您的帮助
Now you understand why we need your help.
我们需要把它隐藏起来
We need to hide it.
有人 狼人试图找到它
There are men, werewolf trying to find it.
-嘿
-Hey!
你在干什么 他死了
What are you doing? He's dead.
他可以再次死一次
He can die again.
我们必须保护它
We have to preserve it.
甲醛
Formaldehyde.
你真期待它能持续多久
How long can you really expect that to last?
时间足够让它送回
Long enough to get it back.
把它给斯大林看
To show it to Stalin.
问问他们 我们可以把它放在哪里
Ask them where we can put it.
它需要隐藏 直到我们找到新的交通工具
It needs hiding until we can find new transport.
嘿 这很重要
Hey! This is important.
不 这个
No, this
危险
dangerous.
你
You...
-销毁它 -不要 不要 留着
-Destroy it. -Nie, nie. Burn.
我不能
I can't do that.
我想她明白
I think she knows.
我知道
I know.
留着它意味着什么
And what it means.
这就是为什么我们必须隐藏它
That's why we have to hide it.
好
Okay.
哇
Whoa.
他不适合
He won't fit.
需要把他拿出来
He needs to come out.
好 一二三
Okay. One, two, three.
我们为什么不烧掉它呢 是他应得的
Why don't we burn it? What he deserves.
这也是他想要的 彻底消失
It's also what he wanted. To disappear.
人们不要他这样
People to not see him like this.
都想亲手杀死他
Killed by his own hand.
那么 你为什么还要隐藏它呢
So why are you hiding it?
为了保护它
To protect it.
必须运回去 为了证明
It has to go back. For proof.
证明
Proof?
-有牙科记录 -斯大林需要看到它
-The dental records. -Stalin needs to see it.
他需要…
He needs--
什么
What?
在俄罗斯 我们喜欢直视敌人的眼睛
In Russia, we like to look our enemy in the eye.
你不会明白的
You wouldn't understand.
你是对的
You're right.
我不明白
I don't understand.
如果你把它搞没了怎么办 如果…
What if you lose it? What if--
如果你为了保护秘密而死呢 对吧
what if you die trying to protect the secret, huh?
你的秘密呢
What about your secret?
这个地方是用来藏人的
This place is for hiding people.
我的猜测是它使你一直能隐藏
My guess is it's been hiding you.
这就是您知道它的原因
That's why you know about it.
你在躲避谁 嗯
Who are you hiding from? Hmm?
你到底是谁 卢卡斯
Who are you really, Lucasz?
德侨
Volksdeutsche.
这就是他们对我们的称呼
That's what they call us.
具有德国血统的波兰人
Polish with German heritage.
勉强 但足够了
Barely, but enough.
当他们入侵时 他们给了我一个简单的选择…
When they invaded they gave me one simple choice--
加入他们
join them
或者去劳教所
or go to the labor camp.
所以当我注册时
So when I signed up,
他们答应我 我会保住我的家
they promised me that I would keep my home.
他们答应我 我的妻子将免于进集中营
They promised me that my wife would be spared from the camp.
他们撒了谎 他们撒谎
They lied. They lie.
这就是他们所做的
It's what they do.
所以当我听说她被带走了
So when I heard that she'd been taken.
我开小差了 但是...
I deserted, but...
当我到达那里时 为时已晚
by the time I got there it was too late.
她已经死了
She was already dead.
苏联人正在推进 所以...
The Soviets were advancing, so...
如果他们找到我 他们会枪毙我
If they found me, they would have shot me.
德国人被赶回边境
Germans are being pushed back across the border,
但其中一些人留下来了
but some of them stayed.
成为狼人
Becoming werewolf.
对周围的村庄
Surrounding villages.
采取报复行动
Taking reprisals.
对俄罗斯人 但是…
A few Russians, but...
主要是对波兰人
mostly Poles.
村民 他们认为是叛徒
Villagers they consider to be traitors.
所以我回避两者
So I hid from both.
我躲开双方
I hid from both sides.
就像我的国家一样
Just like my country.
我们被狼包围着
We're surrounded by wolves.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我知道那是什么感觉
I know what that's like.
是吗
Do you?
失去亲人
To lose someone?
被狼包围
To be surrounded by wolves.
我们为什么不干脆走出去呢
Why don't we just leave?
-然后去哪里 -战斗
-And go where? -The fight.
-战争结束了 我的朋友 -那为什么要追逐这个呢
-The war is over, my friend. -Then why chase this?
因为现在这不是战争
Because this isn't the war now.
这就是一切
This is everything.
我们在森林里找到了他
We found him in the forest.
你问他在哪里吗
Did you ask him where it is?
他只会说俄语
He only speaks Russian.
你知道什么是阿内纳贝吗
Do you know what the Ahnenerbe  is?
这意味着我知道关于人体的一切
It means I know everything there is to know about the human body.
你有一个精致的头骨
You have an exquisite skull.
我和我的同事已经走过了漫长的道路
My colleague and I have come a very long way
因为我们对特定人体的兴趣
because of our interest in a specific human body.
我们相信您可能知道的
One that we believe you might know about.
元首在哪里
Where is the Führer?
他的身体在哪里
Where is the body?
在哪里 元首在哪里
Where is it? Where is the Führer?
这不会造成太大的伤害
This won't hurt as much,
但它会让你永远失明
but it will blind you permanently.
他们找到了其他人
They found the others.
米洛什认为村里有一辆马车
Milosz thinks there's a horse and cart in the village
他可以讨价还价
that he can bargain for.
你的同志伊利亚索夫想和他一起走
Your comrade Ilyasov wants to go with him.
哈哈哈哈
No. No.
他在那里
He's out there.
托尔
Tor.
不 我指的是项链
No, I meant the necklace.
布尔什维克
Bolsheviks.
我们有你的同志
We have your comrade.
把身体给我们 我们就让他活着
Give us the body and we'll let him live.
混蛋
Shit.
你认为你能拍到那个镜头吗
Do you think you could make that shot?
我们必须把他们俩都拿出来
We'd have to take both of them out.
我们俩谁想念 他就死了
Either of us miss and he's dead.
我们应该放弃它
We should just give it up.
无论如何 他们都会杀了他
They're gonna kill him anyway,
不妨拯救我们其他人
may as well save the rest of us.
这只是斯大林的奖杯
It's just a trophy for Stalin.
回到楼下
Get back downstairs.
确保没有人进入 现在
Make sure no one gets in. Now!
把我的枪还给我
Give me back my gun.
你们俩跟他一起去
You two go with him.
守住这些窗户和入口
Secure those windows and entrances.
这件事比我们任何人都重要
This thing is more important than any of us.
那么 我们希望他们不要弄清楚东西在哪里
Let's hope they don't figure out where it is, then.
来吧 托尔 给我一些东西
Come on, Tor. Give me something.
呃 门口有一只狼
Uh, there's a wolf at the door.
他们似乎并不在乎
They don't seem to care.
我会继续给你打洞
I'm gonna keep on putting holes in you
直到你失去那个微笑
until you lose that smile.
-开火
-Fire!
让我看看
Let me look.
停止射击 你会击中它
Stop shooting, you'll hit it.
停 停
Halt! Halt!
这里
Here.
命令那些狼现在就进入那所房子
Order those wolves to get in that house now!
下楼
Get downstairs.
确保他们把这些门挡住了
Make sure they barricaded those doors.
-有人受伤吗 -我们很好
-Is anyone hurt? -We're fine.
瓦迪姆在哪里 伊利亚索夫在哪里
Where's Vadim? Where's Ilyasov?
什么 这是什么
What? What is it?
伊利亚索夫
Ilyasov.
他到底在做什么
What the hell is he doing?
他想要交换 用信息换取他的生命
He wants an exchange. His life for information.
哪些信息值得他一生
And what information would be worth his life?
他知道尸体在哪里
He knows where the body is.
他出卖了我们
He sold us out.
他妈 当我曾经有机会 当时应该杀了他
Fucking knew I should have killed him when I had the chance.
就是这样 他们开枪打死了他 因为他去了棚子
That's it. They shot him because he went for the shed.
它就在那里
It's in there.
退后 绕到它周围
Fall back. Circle around to it.
我想要确认它在那里
I want confirmation it's there.
祝贺 你刚刚买了你的生命
Congratulations. You just bought your life.
如果他们以前没有 他们知道它现在就在那里
If they didn't before, they know it's there now.
我们需要搬出去
We need to move out.
我会把它装上卡车 你在教堂见我
I'll get it on the truck, you meet me at the church.
等待我的信号 然后完成它
Wait for my signal, then finish it.
烧掉它们
Burn them.
他妈的
Fuck.
房子着火了
Fire on the house!
做点什么
Do something.
嘿
Hey!
柳德米拉
Ludmila!
下楼
Get downstairs.
约瑟夫 该死的 开火
Iossif, damn it, fire back!
没关系 没关系
It's okay. It's okay.
呃
Shh.
-打开 是我 这是托尔
-Open up! It's me. It's Tor.
等等 艾欧西夫
Wait, Iossif!
幸运的混蛋
Lucky bastard.
-他们试图把我们烧坏
-They're trying to burn us out.
他们不是冒着烧伤尸体的风险吗
Aren't they risking burning the body?
-它不在房子里 -哦 狗屎
-It's not in the house. -Oh, shit.
这就是为什么我们现在必须去
That's why we have to go now.
睡个好觉 朋友
Sleep well, friend.
在我身上
On me.
-三... -头朝树的掩护
-Three... -Head for the cover of the trees.
...二
...two.
他们走了
They're gone.
布拉纳 等
Brana. Wait.
不
No!
卡车 他们逃脱了
The truck! They're getting away!
等
Wait!
布拉纳
Brana!
-停下 -放开我
-Stop! -Let go of me!
结束了 结束了
It's over! It's over!
-对我来说还没完 -为什么
-It's not over for me! -Why?
哦 他妈的
Oh, fuck!
在教堂里
In a church?
布拉纳
Brana!
布拉纳 你没事
Brana, you're okay.
不
No.
结束了
It's over.
不
No.
托尔无意中听到了他们的声音
Tor overheard them.
他知道他们要去哪里
He knows where they're headed.
他们在教堂里
They're at the church.
什么教会
What church?
我们应该离开 在其他地方这样做
We should leave and do this elsewhere.
我们不会拖着一具尸体走得太远
We won't get far with a body in tow.
它正在迅速退化
It's degrading fast.
我们必须现在就迅速地这样做
We must do this now and quickly.
记录证据证明这不是元首
Record evidence that this is not the Führer.
他没有死
That he's not dead.
- 这是假的 -但就是他
-That it's a fake. -But it is him.
奇观是人们渴望的
Spectacle is what the people crave.
你给他们这个 他们会相信你告诉他们的任何东西
You give them that and they'll believe whatever you tell them.
我们绝不能让他是什么的想法
We mustn't let the idea of what he was,
我们都为之奋斗
what we all fought for,
和我们其他人一起死去
die with the rest of us.
我们也要死吗
Are we to die as well?
-是的
-Yes!
因为这就是我们与众不同的地方
Because that is what sets us apart.
每一盎司 每一滴血都用完了
Every ounce, every drop of blood used up.
因为任何低于完全牺牲的东西
Because anything less than total sacrifice
就是输了
is to lose.
此外
And besides,
死亡什么都不是
death is nothing
如果遗产继续存在
if the legacy lives on.
我认识这个女孩
I know this girl.
另一个无辜的生命
Another innocent life.
这就是为什么我们必须把它拿回来
That's why we have to get it back.
所以我们也可以死吗
So we can die as well?
所以他没有赢
So he doesn't win.
谁
Who?
他死了 布拉纳
He's dead, Brana.
你已经看到了我所看到的
You've seen what I've seen.
他杀害了数百万人
He murdered millions.
不是在战斗中 而是在冷血中
Not in battle, but in cold blood.
他屠杀无辜…
He murdered innocent--
他会杀死每一个人
he would sacrifice every man,
每个女人 孩子
every woman, child,
使整个国家流血致死
an entire nation bled to death,
电源
for power.
为了胜利
For winning.
像这样的男人不会死
Men like that don't die.
它们在地下溃烂 感染一切
They fester in the ground infecting everything.
我希望他们在他被埋葬之前看到他
I want them to see him before he's buried.
我想漂白阳光下的每一根骨头
I want to bleach every bone in the sun
这样他们就会知道
so that they will know
他只是一个男人
he was just a man.
一个男人的懦夫
A coward of a man.
我想那也会让我成为一个懦夫 不去帮忙
I guess that would make me a coward, too, not to help.
你仍然是一个好人
You'd still be a good man.
以前从来没有人指责过我
No one ever accused me of that before.
嗯 我是
Well, I am.
你有计划吗
Have you got a plan?
我可能会
I might.
尸检证明 这是另一个谎言
As the autopsy proves, this is yet another lie.
这显然不是元首的身体
It's quite clearly not the body of the Führer.
牙齿和器官都显示
Both the teeth and the organs show
这个人在年龄上是不同的 而且…
that this man was different in age and--
气 气 气
Gas! Gas! Gas!
骷髅头 我需要骷髅头
The skull! I need the skull!
下 下
Down! Down!
射
Shoot!
不
No!
帮助他们
Help them.
帮助 帮助他们
Help. Help them.
让他保持静止
Hold him still.
抱着他
Hold him!
操你妈
Fuck you!
结束了 小家伙
It's over, little man.
-不
-No!
把它给我 把它给我
Give it to me. Give it to me.
把身体给我 我会让你走的
Give me the body. I will let you go.
我会让你活着 开门
I will let you live. Open the door.
开门 不
Open the door! No!
不 不
No, no!
不 不 不要碰这个 不
No, no. Don't touch this. No!
不 不 不
No, no! No!
把身体给我
Give me the body.
不
No!
不 不
No! No!
不
No!
帮助 帮助
Help! Help!
不 不
No! No!
对不起 布拉纳
Sorry, Brana.
不
No!
同时思考很奇怪
Strange to think at that same time
凯特尔正在签署德国投降书
Keitel was signing the German surrender.
没有人来找我们
Nobody came looking for us.
假设我们都死了
Presuming we were all dead.
或者只是希望我们是
Or just hoping we were.
火灾发生后
After the fire
剩下的只是碎片
all that was left were fragments.
件
Pieces.
还有骨头
And bones.
当我回到莫斯科时
When I got back to Moscow
掩护 旨在让盟军站在一边
the cover-up, designed to keep the Allies on side,
已经持续了太久
had gone on too long.
如果斯大林被骗了 那将是尴尬的
Would be embarrassing for Stalin to be caught in a lie.
所以他们埋葬了我
So they buried me.
以及我带来的任何证据
And any evidence I brought with me.
西伯利亚古拉格的六年寒冷
Six cold years in a Siberian gulag.
这就是我离开她的地方
That's where I left her.
布拉纳·布罗德斯卡娅
Brana Brodskaya.
那是她死的地方
That's where she died.
伴随着她的希望和她的理想
Along with her hopes and her ideals.
以及任何向世界展示真相的概念
And any notions of exposing the truth to the world.
当我被释放时 我回到了波兰
When I was released, I went back to Poland.
到弗罗茨瓦夫
To Wroclaw.
拜访老朋友
To visit an old friend.
这属于救了我一命的人
This belonged to the man who saved my life.
当我需要一个人时 他就在那里
He was there when I needed someone.
我最黑暗的时刻
My darkest hour.
帮我捡起碎片
Helped me to pick up the pieces.
有空来看我
Set me free.
当我听说他已经死了
When I heard that he had died,
在被攻击后
after being attacked in a supposed break-in,
我很不高兴
I was quite upset.
历史不是由胜利者书写的
History isn't written by the victors.
它被那些幸存下来的人记住了
It's remembered by those that survive it.
当他们离开时
And when they're gone,
我们如何避免重复历史
how do we avoid repeating history?
我们如何记住
How do we remember?
那里
There.
全部完成
All done.
现在结束了
Over now.
应该不会花很长时间
Shouldn't take long.
哦 我差点忘了
Oh, I almost forgot.
他送了我这份礼物
He sent me this gift.
纪念品
A memento.
但我敢肯定这是为你准备的
But I'm sure it was meant for you.
对于像你这样的人
For people like you.
所以至少你得到了你来的目的
So at least you got what you came for.
一个盒子
A box.
一个神奇的盒子
A magical box.
现在是时候了
It's time now.
♪ 我们又来了 ♪
♪ Here we are again ♪
♪ 家人和朋友 ♪
♪ Family and friends ♪
♪ 是时候进行补救了 ♪
♪ Time to make amends ♪
♪ 盘点并重置 ♪
♪ Take stock and reset ♪
♪ 所有穿着都穿着得体 ♪
♪ All smartly dressed ♪
♪ 化妆跑步 ♪
♪ With makeup run ♪
♪ 分享哀悼 ♪
♪ Sharing condolences ♪
♪ 和思念你 我们缺少的一个 ♪
♪ And thoughts of you, Our missing one ♪
♪ 缺席是最明确的 ♪
♪ Absence is most defined ♪
♪ 起初感觉 ♪
♪ And felt at first ♪
♪ 这是地面♪上的影子
♪ It's the shadow On the ground ♪
♪ 当您在灵车♪中滑行时
♪ As you glide by In your hearse ♪
♪ 时间 它吞噬 ♪
♪ The time, it devours ♪
♪ 您的形状和边缘 ♪
♪ Your shape and your edges ♪
♪ 所有内存都已弯曲 ♪
♪ All memory is bent ♪
♪ 适合或隐藏的议程 ♪
♪ To suit or hidden agendas ♪
♪ 所以对于我们缺席的朋友 ♪
♪ So to our absent friend ♪
♪ 抛弃的人♪
♪ The one who cast away ♪
♪ 知道我们很♪想念你
♪ Know we miss you so ♪
♪ 我们真的希望你留下来 ♪
♪ We really wish you'd stayed ♪
♪ 你知道你流过我们的心 ♪
♪ You know you flow through Our hearts ♪
♪ 一遍又一遍 ♪
♪ Over and over again ♪
♪ 在这血♪海中
♪ In this sea of blood ♪
♪ 流经我们的血管 ♪
♪ That flows through Our veins ♪
♪ 它将您带入我们的内心 ♪
♪ It carries you within us ♪
♪ 虽然我会一直想念那张脸 ♪
♪ Though I'll always miss That face ♪
♪ 用它很好傻的笑容 ♪
♪ With it's fine dumb grin ♪
♪ 哦 我们处于一个多么大的状态♪
♪ Oh, what a state we're in ♪
♪ 适合爆裂 ♪
♪ Fit to burst ♪
♪ 我只是希望我们能谈论它 ♪
♪ I just wish we could Have talked about it ♪
♪ 我们不知道你受伤了 ♪
♪ We didn't know That you were hurting ♪
♪ 在阴凉处♪过着生活
♪ Lived a life Within the shade ♪
♪ 现在你已经放下了自己的窗帘 ♪
♪ Now you've lowered Your own curtains ♪
♪ 我希望你找到你所渴望的♪和平
♪ I hope you found the peace That you craved ♪
♪ 从这一切中喘口气♪
♪ A respite from it all ♪
♪ 为您摔倒提供缓冲♪
♪ A cushion to your fall ♪
♪ 知道是多么可悲♪
♪ How sad it is to know ♪
♪ 你永远不会变老 ♪
♪ You'll never grow old ♪
♪ 所以对于我们缺席的朋友 ♪
♪ So to our absent friend ♪
♪ 抛弃的人♪
♪ The one who cast away ♪
♪ 知道我们很♪想念你
♪ Know we miss you so ♪
♪ 我们真的希望你留下来 ♪
♪ We really wish You'd stayed ♪
♪ 知道你流过我们的心 ♪
♪ Know you flow through Our hearts ♪
♪ 一遍又一遍 ♪
♪ Over and over again ♪
♪ 在这血♪海中
♪ In this sea of blood ♪
♪ 流经我们的血管 ♪
♪ That flows through Our veins ♪
♪ 我仍然不太相信 ♪
♪ I still Can't quite believe ♪
♪ 我们再也见不到彼此了 ♪
♪ We'll never see Each other again ♪
♪ 这让我四分五裂 ♪
♪ And that tears me apart ♪
♪ 一遍又一遍 ♪
♪ Over and over again ♪